We're at the Incheon Munhak Stadium.
I sometimes come to Incheon to film TV shows.
Show directors love filming outdoors.
- But the weather is indeed nice.
- So...
- The weather is great.
- Yes.
But hear me out. I film outdoors almost all week.
As for them, they only film one show a week.
That's the difference.
I filmed outdoors yesterday.
I'll film another show outdoors in two days.
I never film inside a studio set.
- I mostly film outdoors.
- You mostly film outdoors.
Right. I've spent my whole life outdoors.
As long as we're in the shade and away from the sun,
- it's pretty cool.
- It's nice and cool.
It's cool in the shade. It's indeed autumn now.
- My gosh.
- I can feel it now.
- Yes.
- And the sky is very clear.
- Right.
- The sky feels high too.
- Yes. It does.
Right.
Shall we go in?
I guess we're all wearing red.
Isn't that such an intense color?
(Two men dressed in an intense shade of red)
Games...
(Even from behind, they look fierce.)
Should I wave at them like this?
- Are they filming us now?
- Here.
I'm nervous.
- You're nervous?
- Yes.
Why?
I'm going to meet Jae Seok in person.
- Or they'd just curse.
- Right.
- They wouldn't say hello.
- Who's that?
I was right.
- I was right.
- Was it really Byun Yo Han?
- This was the intel you got.
- I was right. I...
- Yes. It's for "Tazza." I told you.
- Oh, my.
- I was right. It's Yo Han.
- Hello.
- It was for "Tazza."
- Right.
- Hello.
- "Tazza."
- Gosh. Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
Have you seen my works?
Of course.
(This new hire made a smooth entrance into the industry.)
(As the early years of his acting career passed, )
(he became the face of an era in "Mr. Sunshine.")
(He was even showered with petals alongside a familiar face.)
(He was fiercely dedicated to protect his country.)
(Then he burned with passion to protect her too.)
(Actor Byun Yo Han)
(His performance as a villain was acknowledged by the world.)
(Playing the role of a delusional patient)
(He puts on a different face for different projects.)
(Playing the role of a crazy shaman)
(A psychopathic doctor)
(A sleazy government agent)
(The most sought-after actor on the rise)
(Actor Roh Jae Won)
Nice to meet you. Hello.
- Brother. It's been a while.
- Have you seen my works?
Of course. Is this the first time we're meeting?
I've seen you once.
- Right? At an awards ceremony?
- But...
- slightly...
- Where did we meet?
No. We met at the COVID-19 testing clinic.
- Really?
- I saw you by chance.
But back then, I was in college.
- Really?
- Yes.
- We met at the testing clinic?
- You got the test done together?
- Yes. We got it done together.
I was in college back then.
- I knew who you were.
- Right.
I thought it'd be weird if I didn't say hello.
- I said hello before I realized it.
- You said hello?
I did. When you saw me, you did this.
- You weren't sure if you knew me.
- Right.
- That was your reaction.
- Then did I leave?
- You should talk to him up close.
- Okay.
- I can't believe we met before.
- Come this way.
- At the clinic...
- Jae Won.
- Let's sit down first.
- Let's sit down.
Actually,
Yeon Seok mentioned you guys last week.
He said that your movie was going to premiere soon.
- I got the intel.
- He told me that...
you were going to star on our show.
I was super arrogant about the intel.
(Acting arrogant)
- He was so arrogant.
- I...
- You're joining us this week.
- Yes.
- I said I played them like a pro.
- You thought we'd be here.
- I played them like a pro.
- But I was wrong.
(The real professionals are finally here.)
It's been so long, Yo Han.
- You've been well, right?
- I've been well.
You look even better now.
Why didn't you invite me to your wedding?
We had a simple wedding.
Why didn't you invite me?
We had a simple wedding with just our families.
Actually, he texted me.
- Right.
- He congratulated me...
and told me to invite me to the wedding.
We only invited our families.
Great.
So you guys invited only your families, right?
Yes. We wouldn't invite some fake families to our wedding.
You know what? This trend started with Jong Kook.
Having private weddings has become a trend among celebrities.
A lot of people hold a small, family-only wedding.
- That's right.
- Yes.
I really thought that I had met you, Jae Won.
It turned out we met...
- At the COVID-19 testing clinic.
- Right.
How long has it been? Was that...
- It was 4 or 5 years ago.
- in 2020?
It was around Hakdong Station.
- He even remembers the clinic.
- Around Hakdong Station.
Yes.
- The medical clinic?
- Yes.
Back then, we couldn't go to the theaters.
- Right. It hit movie theaters hard.
- Gosh, that wasn't the worst of it.
Back then, movie theaters were...
- going through a dry spell.
- That's right.
Things have improved now.
- Movie theaters...
- Some sold ten million tickets.
- The industry is picking up now.
- Things are picking up now.
Yes. And your movie, "Tazza," will be released now.
- At last.
- Yes.
- When will it be released?
- On September 23.
("Tazza" is in theaters now.)
Jae Won, your recent projects...
have been performing well.
- Right.
- Seriously.
You're in all of successful projects these days.
- Right.
- You really are.
So you guys filmed "Tazza" together.
In terms of the series, is this...
This is the finale of the series.
- It's the finale?
- Yes.
This movie is about the inferiority complex...
and revenge of two friends.
What's this?
(The two of them used to be close friends...)
(ever since they were in school, )
(but became the devil who tried to bring each other down.)
Hey, Park Tae.
(The twisted inferiority complex...)
(ruined their friendship.)
(Jang Tae Young, born under a lucky star)
(Park Tae Young, born under a bad sign)
(This time, it's cards, not hwatu.)
(The stakes will be higher.)
(The grand finale of the "Tazza" series)
("Tazza: The Song of Beelzebub")
The previous ones were about hwatu.
- It's about hold 'em.
- This one is about card games.
- Yes.
- I didn't know that.
I bet you had to learn some card tricks for the movie.
Yes. We practiced a lot and took lessons.
By the time this episode airs,
your movie would already have been released.
- Really?
- I see.
People promote their projects midway now.
I heard a lot of people watched the movie already during Chuseok.
So many people seem to love our movie.
- Right.
- I'd like to thank them again.
(Thanking the audience in advance)
You're good.
- Gosh, it's a hit.
- Yes.
The Korean movie industry...
- is picking up now.
- That's great.
It'd be nice if the whole industry thrived.
We're at the Incheon Munhak Stadium. Which one of you...
- Who has ties to Incheon?
- Do you guys have ties to Incheon?
It's not you, Yo Han. Is it?
- Both of us...
- We're both from here.
- Really? Incheon?
- Yes.
I didn't know you were from Incheon, Yo Han.
- You too, Jae Won?
- Yes.
Which part of Incheon?
- I grew up in Seo-gu.
- Seo-gu.
- What about you, Yo Han?
- Yo Han?
- I'm from Namdong-gu.
- Namdong-gu.
- There are many famous spots here.
- That's right.
Yes. Could you introduce a few in Namdong-gu?
(Recommend famous spots in Namdong-gu.)
It's around Incheon Culture and Arts Center.
There's an Outback Steakhouse.
(An unexpected famous spot)
- I love Outback Steakhouse.
- Yo Han... Yes.
And this is a famous spot for the locals.
- Right here.
- Yes.
- Right.
- We played against Portugal here.
That's right.
- It was held here.
- It was crazy here.
Did you watch the game?
I had to watch it over the fence.
Everyone wore the Be the Reds shirt.
It was red just like our dress code.
Traffic was completely gridlocked.
- It was crazy.
- Yes.
How old were you in 2002, Jae Won?
- In 2002... I was born in 1993.
- He was born in 1993.
- Were you in elementary school?
- Yes, I was in second grade.
Second grade? You don't remember the games, right?
- No, I remember them.
- You do?
Yes.
I remember that Korea lost to Germany.
Just talk about the games we won.
- Right. Yes.
- There are...
- Just talk about the games we won.
- There are many good memories.
- Why mention the game we lost?
- He takes good care of Jae Won.
Well, that was the most memorable game to me.
- I wanted us to win.
- We would've advanced to the final.
Yes.
Anyway, they were born and raised...
here in Incheon.
- Let's check it out.
- Let's go...
- Let's go.
- and find our first Whenever Guest.
All right. Our first Whenever Guest is Lee Jung Min.
"On weekdays, we find a way to navigate around the gridlock."
"On our days off,"
"we're sky-blue sheriffs who guard the roads in Incheon."
"We've voluntarily given up weekends and national holidays..."
"to be on the road."
"So we need a lot of energy."
"If you ever find yourselves in Incheon, give us a call."
Are they traffic police officers?
- They must be.
- They sound like police officers.
- Yes.
- They do, right?
- Right.
Where is it?
Namdong-gu.
Yes, right.
- Namchon-dong.
(The Namdong-gu local doesn't feel confident.)
I need to look it up.
(Embarrassed)
I'm getting the sense that you haven't been here for a while.
- Yo Han.
- I don't know where it is...
just by looking at the address.
- You don't?
- No.
I'm going to look it up.
Hold on. Can we take a bus there?
(GPS Byun is on too.)
(GPS Roh is on too.)
- It's okay. The number is 512.
- Let me see.
Are you all looking it up on the map?
Yeon Seok already looked it up. You guys don't have to look it up.
I can just do this.
It's nice to have help.
- On the map, it looks like...
- I see. Here...
We can take Bus Four to get there.
- Bus Four?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
(They head to the bus stop nearby.)
- You've been well, right?
- Yes. Gosh.
Aren't you going to start filming a drama soon?
- Yes.
- Which college...
The one I filmed with Hyun Jin...
will premiere next month.
My gosh. You're always working. You don't take a break.
- You don't take a break either.
- I don't.
But you're on variety shows too.
But you got married.
- Right.
- Yes.
- I'm older than him.
- Are you guys the same age?
- He's older than me.
- I'm older than him.
But he has more life experience than me now.
- Right.
- Yes.
Yo Han and I would've worn our hair in a topknot...
if this were back in the past.
- Your hair would've been braided.
- Right.
- I couldn't wear it in a topknot.
(Two older men with a bachelor with braided hair)
Let's go this way.
- Have you watched our show?
- Yes.
(They keep chatting.)
Are you good at games?
I don't think I'm as good as you.
It's crazy how determined you are...
about these games.
You even got a superpower.
You know what? See it for yourself.
- Does that happen to everyone?
- You become determined.
I bet you'll be more determined than me.
I'm serious. You can see...
our Whenever Guests desperately hoping we succeed.
I'm sure that's a lot of pressure.
- That sense of pressure...
- That's...
Where do you live now?
I still live here.
- You still live here?
- Yes.
(Jae Won still lives in Incheon.)
My family still lives here.
- Everyone lives here.
- And so do I. Yes.
Bus Four comes here.
- This is the bus stop.
- Yes.
When will Bus Four come?
It said earlier that we had to wait 14 minutes.
- Fourteen minutes?
- Yes. Now...
We have to wait ten minutes.
Eleven minutes.
It's cool in the shade.
Yes. It's cool as long as we stay in the shade.
My gosh. That's not cool.
Oh, that?
(Trash thrown onto the roof of the bus stop)
Did they end up on the roof from one of our games?
- Those bottles...
- Like this game.
They just threw away the bottles after finishing them.
They just threw the bottles away when the bus came.
(They threw the bottles high up, making it difficult to clean up.)
- Should we get them down?
- Should we do that?
- Are you tall enough?
- Wait.
Carry me on your shoulders.
Hey.
- I can easily get them down then.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- The loser has to do it.
- Let's do that.
- The loser has to get the bottles.
- No.
- The winner gets the shoulder ride.
- Okay.
- That's right. It's the winner.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Lost, lost, won, won)
- We'll have to give them a lift.
- Okay.
- The winner has to do it.
- I knew it.
Doesn't it make more sense for us to go on your shoulders?
You're too heavy to get a shoulder ride.
Then Yo Han should get the ride.
- He seems pretty heavy too.
- I...
Right. I'm a bit heavy.
The three of us can give you a lift.
- All right. Let's try that.
- Yes.
Yo Han, you have to do it.
(Model Citizens of Incheon set out.)
How should we lift him up?
- Let's give him a boost.
- No. He should step on our palms.
- Step on your palms?
- We can't lift him with our arms?
Let's try that first.
That's not going to work.
- One, two, three.
- It's going to work.
- He got it.
There you go. Well done.
- You got it.
- Nicely done.
(Model Citizens of Incheon clean up perfectly.)
(The leader finishes up the job.)
- This isn't right. Seriously.
- That was fun.
I'm not sure if whoever threw out the bottles...
- will watch our show.
- Right.
You shouldn't throw out trash like that.
Come on.
- So...
- We did a good deed.
- How could they clean this up?
- Right.
My beloved city.
- I think that's the bus.
- Bus Four.
- Right.
- You got this?
- Yes. I got it.
I pay for the bus rides.
(They move toward to the bus stop.)
- We don't pay individually?
- I pay for everyone.
- He has the transportation card.
- Yes.
- This doesn't cost much.
- Wait.
- It's just passing by.
(Screaming)
What was that?
Do buses not stop if drivers don't see anyone?
(The bus driver didn't see them and drove past them.)
Wait.
Is this normal?
The bus just left like that?
(The three of them are shocked.)
- I guess you had to wave.
- What?
- You had to be in the front.
(They were taking their sweet time behind the bus stop and missed it.)
Hold on. We had to be there by...
I had no idea.
We have to wave at the bus...
if we want to get on the bus in Incheon?
- I should've...
- Earlier, the lady...
We should've sat down here earlier.
We had no idea.
(Pickup Point)
- Let's sit down.
- Wait.
(The pickup point is further ahead than expected.)
- Jae Won.
- I'm flustered.
What about Bus Five?
Bus Five is good too.
But it will take 33 minutes.
- That takes too long?
- Yes.
We have to be there by 11:30am.
- Then...
- Here's what I noticed.
The drivers only stop if you wave them down fiercely.
We have no choice then.
(They end up waiting for the bus again.)
- It will be here in five minutes.
- Yes.
I landed in Korea yesterday.
- Really? From where?
- We went on a late honeymoon trip.
You were on your honeymoon? Where did you go?
We went to a warm country. We went to Hawaii.
Hawaii, yes.
We went to San Francisco because she grew up there.
I bet it was great.
- It was great.
- Right.
I wouldn't have come back if it weren't for this show.
Thank you.
- Wait. Not yet.
- Is it here?
No.
- we're traumatized.
- Right.
- Whenever we see a bus...
- We have to open our arms up.
Whenever we see a bus...
It's at the previous stop.
Okay.
(They'll stand at the pickup point in advance.)
- My gosh, seriously.
- Let's move up now.
(Actively flagging down the driver)
- The bus is coming toward us.
- Yes. What a relief.
That's a relief.
- Hello.
- Thank you.
My gosh. This is nice.
- We got on an empty bus.
- I wouldn't have felt this great...
if I got on the bus easily.
- Right.
- Exactly.
Do you often use public transportation?
- I always take the bus and subway.
- Really?
- Yes.
But why didn't you tell us we had to flag down the drivers?
- Pardon?
- Why didn't you let us know?
- I...
- I didn't know...
- it'd just drive past us. No.
- You didn't know?
I didn't know.
Living here...
There will be announcements, right?
The announcements?
(He's nervous to take the bus for the first time in Incheon.)
What if getting off the bus is hard too?
- Wait. Where do we need to get off?
- How many stops do we need to go?
We got on the bus, so we need to get off at the right stop.
- Okay.
- Where is it?
I've been monitoring the route.
- Okay. Namchon-dong Entrance.
- Namchon-dong.
Namchon-dong.
When did you move out of Incheon?
I lived here until high school.
I went to school here up through high school.
- Up through high school?
- Yes.
You too, Jae Won?
I went to school here up through middle school.
I went to high school in Anyang.
- Was it Anyang Arts High School?
- Yes.
You went to Anyang Arts High School.
What were you like in high school?
During your school years?
I had so much fun in school.
- I went to an arts high school.
- Anyang Arts High School.
- They all majored in Acting.
- Right.
Were you quiet in school?
I didn't think that...
I was quiet in school.
I had fun.
- I was playful.
- Really?
There's a subtle streak of mischief...
all over your face.
- Right. I can be quite mischievous.
- Yes.
But only around people I'm close to.
- You need time to open up.
- Yes.
He's playful around his close friends.
I've gotten close to Yo Han.
Yo Han...
(Looking around)
Is this the Culture and Arts Center?
- Yes.
- Isn't the bus terminal here?
Right, the bus terminal.
The bus terminal is here? You know where we are now?
- And...
- Right. There's a bus terminal.
I performed in a play at the Culture and Arts Center...
when I was in middle school for the first time.
Ever since then...
- That's where your dream started?
- I dreamed of becoming an actor.
- Right.
- There's an open plaza...
in front of the department store.
I used to breakdance there.
- You used to breakdance?
- Yes.
I used to do the windmill there.
This is the birthplace of my dreams.
This is the main street, right?
- It used to be the busiest area...
- Right?
- in Incheon back then.
- Michuhol-gu.
What was Incheon like when you were growing up?
Incheon was nicknamed the Devildom.
(The legend of Incheon by an Incheon native)
There's a produce and fish market around here.
People fight with napa cabbages and radishes.
- Why?
- That's how it's done in Incheon.
(Bragging about his hometown with dignity)
With napa cabbages and radishes?
- But people here are very friendly.
- Of course.
They're very affectionate.
That's their way of expressing affection.
- With napa cabbages and radishes.
- Isn't...
Jemulpo High School famous here?
- It's a famous school.
- Jemulpo High School.
- The school is located...
- in the east of Incheon.
- I see.
Are vibes different between eastern...
- and western Incheon?
- So...
We call them the East Side and the West Side.
When you go there,
older guys take your money as soon as you get off the bus.
(Older guys take your money as soon as you get off the bus.)
I always had to hide my pocket money in my socks.
(Incheon was quite different back in the day.)
- You know what?
- There's nothing I can do.
That's the neighborhood...
- I grew up in.
- You know what?
I grew up in Seoul.
- Which part of Seoul?
- I grew up in Suyu-ri.
- That's a rough neighborhood. Yes.
- I saw a lot of bullies growing up.
When we were in school,
- They were everywhere.
- there were so many bullies.
- There were so many bullies.
- Yes.
- Seriously.
- And that was the era.
We had to be competitive and fierce to survive.
- We had to be.
- We had to be competitive.
- We need to survive today's games.
- I...
- I'm going to do my best.
- Yes.
I'll do my best.
- Do we need to get off?
- Shall we?
- Gosh.
- Thank you.
- Tag the card.
Okay. Thank you.
My gosh. Where are we going?
It looks like we're going to the wilderness.
- Right. I don't see anything here.
- It looks empty here.
(Sky-blue sheriffs are in a place like this?)
Wait. Could it be the Best Driver Association?
Could it be that over there?
- Where?
- There's an office.
Over there?
- I see.
- That must be it.
On weekends, they...
- Right.
- Yes.
- They volunteer on weekends.
I see.
- "Best Driver Association."
- We're here.
You know what?
- It's here?
- It says, "Council."
"Council."
(Gently knocking on the door)
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hello.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Are you Mr. Lee Jung Min?
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- My gosh.
- Hello.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Please sit down.
- Okay. This way.
My gosh. Nice to meet you.
(A veteran taxi driver who navigates every corner of Incheon)
(Taxi Driver Lee Jung Min)
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
(They've never been to the office of the Best Driver Association.)
This is the Namdong-gu office...
- of the Best Driver Association.
- Yes.
(Intrigued)
We often go to your alma mater.
- Which one?
- Guwolseo Elementary School.
- Really?
- Yes.
- We... Yes.
- Did you know I was coming?
You knew I was coming today?
I had a gut feeling. You filmed "Tazza 4."
(Locals just get each other.)
- You had a feeling it'd be him.
- Yes.
I was wondering if it would be you guys.
- I see.
- Yes.
- You were right.
- Both of them are from Incheon.
- Yes.
- So...
how long have you worked as a taxi driver?
I became a taxi driver right after my military discharge.
- I became a taxi driver very young.
- Really?
But I didn't work as a taxi driver for a long time.
I drove my taxi for a bit over a year.
I came back to this job in 2000.
- In 2000?
- Yes.
- But still. It's been 26...
- So it's been about 26 years.
- to 27 years now.
- Yes.
So I took a look around the office.
I see that the association is in charge of many duties.
Could you tell us about the duties?
During the morning rush hour,
we keep traffic moving...
- Right.
- at each intersection.
Things can get hectic.
So we work at the intersections to help with traffic duties.
We go to elementary and middle schools...
- For safety.
- to make sure safety.
The largest number of volunteers is deployed at the day of the CSAT.
- On the day of the CSAT.
- On the day of the CSAT, - Right.
All of our members volunteer.
But you don't receive any monetary benefits...
- from the association.
- We don't.
We volunteer on our own initiative.
(It's a volunteer organization without pay.)
We're just a group of volunteers just like me.
A friend of mine said this to me.
"You lived for yourself for the past 50 years."
"Why don't you live a life, helping others..."
"for the remaining years of your life?"
How should I put it? He kept trying to get me to join.
Just like you said,
not any taxi drivers can join this association.
- There are requirements, right?
- Yes.
To join, you must have driven a commercial vehicle...
- for over two years, accident-free.
- Accident-free.
And you can't have a felony record.
- Of course.
- You can't have a criminal record.
- Right. There must be requirements.
- Yes.
- I can see that...
- you're second in line.
- Yes.
- That's the chairman.
- You're the senior vice chairman.
- Yes.
- Right.
Will you be the chairman next term?
- You're on TV now.
- Right.
You're on TV now.
When you're volunteering, I'm sure some people upset you.
- That happens sometimes.
- Yes.
Earlier today, when we were coming here,
we got upset at the bus stop.
- Really?
- Yes. Someone threw out...
two water bottles on the roof of the bus stop.
Yo Han took care of the trash.
People from Namdong-gu have exemplary character.
But Yeon Seok and Jae Won gave him a lift.
(We helped out too.)
I'm sure you encounter unpleasant people...
- when you volunteer.
- Yes. Some curse at us.
- "Who do you think you are?"
- Right.
- They shouldn't do that.
- Seriously.
- Come on. Why, Yeon Seok?
- I know, right?
Me? Wait.
I was a military driver. I follow traffic regulations.
- I was looking for your approval.
- Okay.
I was looking for your approval of my opinion.
Nice to meet you. I was also a military driver.
- This keeps happening.
- That again?
- It keeps happening.
- He talks about himself every week.
- This happened again.
- His time as a military driver,
Sejong University, and his military service in the Air Force.
I wasn't going to talk about myself.
Since Yo Han and Jae Won are joining us today,
I hope we can make it to Round Three.
- You're both from Incheon.
- Right. You're both from Incheon.
- I'll do my best.
- Sounds good.
- We'll give you everything.
- Thank you.
We're starting right away.
- Okay.
- Please open...
the first fortune cookie.
Please read it.
"I'm the Tom Cruise of Incheon when I'm behind the wheel."
"Two pairs of Ray-Ban sunglasses..."
"for me and my close friend, the chairman."
(We're the Tom Cruise of Incheon! Ray-Ban sunglasses)
(Amazed)
- Two pairs.
- Sunglasses for the chairman...
and the vice chairman.
(Friendship sunglasses for the leaders)
- They definitely need sunglasses.
- Yes.
(Parking Master)
(They must park...)
(the toy taxi in the parking zone.)
(Round 1: Park 2 out of 4 toy taxis.)
(Park the taxi?)
Is it a miniature taxi?
(Mini taxi cars)
(They must park mini taxi cars...)
We have pro-gamers today.
- Let's try it.
- I doubt we'll be disappointed.
- My goodness. Listen.
- Okay. I'm good at parking.
- It has no power.
- But...
The wheels can't be on the line like this?
- Here too?
- Yes.
(Driving through)
- Right.
- Gosh.
This will be tough.
This one? I see.
- It also rolls.
- You can push it...
or wind up the car. It's up to you.
Pushing it would be better. Right?
- We can just push it too?
- Yes.
I see. We can use different methods.
(He tries winding up the car.)
I see. This is...
It doesn't look easy.
- It won't be easy.
- It's not easy.
With the chairman here...
Oh, no.
(His presence doubles their pressure.)
We have to decide whether to wind up the car or not.
We can just decide that on our own, right? It's up to us.
It's up to you.
(He winds up the car to practice.)
This isn't easy.
You got it.
- See that? He did it.
- Right? Jae Won got it.
- If I start from here...
- I think I can do it.
We can push it too, right?
(Pushing the car)
Pushing it... How is it?
- I think it's better.
- This is...
Should I just push it?
It won't work.
Pushing it...
For the right direction, winding it up is better than pushing it.
Hold on. I should try starting a little farther back.
We've got to succeed.
Let me, a former military driver, try.
The former military driver.
(Sergeant Ahn takes the stage.)
- Isn't that too...
- Come on.
(The military driver is embarrassed.)
Give me a second.
Allow me to practice a little.
(Letting go)
He's got it.
Okay.
- How did I do it?
- I've gotten the hang of it.
It's okay to be gentle.
- The others can push it in.
- Exactly.
- That sounds better.
- It could work.
The wheels of my car...
While keeping the wheels outside of the line,
- Pull it?
- if I pull the car back...
so that...
it's within the circle...
(Parked perfectly)
(Jae Won established a parking theory.)
- Nice.
- You got it.
You got the direction.
(Practicing as taught by Jae Won)
(Parked successfully)
- I did it.
- You've also gotten the hang of it.
That's it. I've got it.
- You have.
- Listen.
I think we can do it if we adjust the distance.
See that?
How about pushing it in like this?
- Nice.
- That works.
Okay. How many cars?
- Two.
- Let's give it a shot.
- Yes, let's do it.
- I can do it.
- Let's do a group cheer first.
Here.
- In 1, 2, 3. Go!
- I...
- Who's going first? Should I?
- Do you want to?
- Go ahead.
(First driver: Jae Seok)
(Blowing)
- You're going for it, right?
- Yes.
- Yes, we are.
- Got it.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
(1st try, Jae Seok)
- He's got it.
- You did it. It crossed the line.
- It's over the line.
- It's in.
- It crossed the line.
(The wheels are touching the inside of the parking line.)
- Okay.
- It's in, right?
- It's in.
- For sure.
It doesn't count if it's pushed out.
Of course.
So we can't push it out.
Really, please.
Please.
- Yo Han.
- What?
Look, this is how you're like.
- What is it?
- Your hand.
- It might hit your hand.
- He's on edge.
- Yo Han is on edge.
- My bad.
- He's focused right now.
- Yo Han is on edge.
(Focusing again)
Son of Namdong.
Son of Namdong-gu.
(1st try, Yo Han)
(Cheering)
(Hugging)
My gosh.
Namdong.
Guwolseo Elementary School!
Okay. Success.
(Cheering)
Son of Namdong.
- Round One, success!
- Success!
Guwolseo Elementary School!
Jae Won couldn't even try.
He can try in this round.
All right. With that, the sunglasses were...
- a success.
- Success!
We've got this game.
Nice!
We've succeeded in Round One.
Now, whether you'd like to go for Round Two.
- Go.
There are many tries left.
We haven't used the chance yet.
"The essential dessert stop for the drivers..."
"keeping Incheon's roads moving,"
"an instant mixed coffee vending machine."
A vending machine?
- That's it.
- It's a vending machine.
We need to succeed.
You see that in restaurants.
- That's right.
- We must get it for them.
A cup of coffee does wonders.
- It's great.
- Mixed coffee vending machine.
(Round 2)
(There's a no-parking zone.)
(In what used to be a spacious parking area, )
(a no-parking zone appears!)
(The cars can be parked only in these two zones.)
In those zones?
(The parking zones have gotten much smaller.)
- Two parking zones on the sides.
- Seriously,
how do they come up with such a game?
The props add to it.
- They do, right?
- Yes.
The production crew should write a book.
- No, right?
- A game book will be published.
- The game book...
- Whenever Possible game book.
Some people will ask for it.
How do I park the car?
Don't think about how much narrower it is psychologically.
- Aren't I right?
- Right now, I'm...
- We should push it like so.
- Yes.
- Right now...
- Really?
(Laughing)
You didn't cuss just now, did you?
There's this obsession with having to do well.
It's different, right? I told you.
This isn't easy. Hold on.
- What now?
- You can continue,
but within ten tries.
- We...
- What?
(Clapping)
This is my kind of game.
- Okay, we've got it.
- Good.
He's got the best feel for it.
I've got it.
You've got it.
(It's in again.)
- That was perfect.
- Exactly.
I've got it. We should try now.
- Keep a wider view.
- Go!
(Jae Won's car goes in.)
- It's in!
- Nice.
Well done.
- But...
- We weren't going for it.
- Shall we try?
- Yes.
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
- Good luck. Call it.
- Call it.
- Here we go.
- Okay.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 2.)
(2nd try, Jae Won)
Go.
It's curving.
- Well done. Nice.
- I'll go next.
- Good job.
- Yeon Seok.
Since it's blocking the way...
Shift the car into reverse.
(2nd try, Yeon Seok)
Let go here.
Go.
Come on.
- The wheels spun at first.
- It's okay.
- Yo Han?
- No.
I'll go.
They spun at first.
- I can't move them, right?
- Leave them.
(Extremely nervous)
- Two cars need to go in, right?
- Correct.
(Next is Model Driver Jae Seok.)
We have several tries left.
This far should do. Did I pull back a bit too much?
Did I pull it back too much?
- Do it again.
- I don't know.
I'll give it a little wind resistance.
Wind resistance.
(Wind resistance)
(2nd try, Jae Seok)
It'll go in.
The car is...
- That was...
- The car...
a little too much wind resistance.
- You never know.
- It's perfect right now.
The cars are in a line.
- Just crash into them...
- Yes.
- and make two go in.
- You can totally...
- push two in.
- Exactly.
Here I go.
(2nd try, Yo Han)
(Failed)
- Sorry. It's my competitive spirit.
- It's okay.
- Yo Han is...
- Sorry. It's my competitive spirit.
Yo Han's showing the most competitive spirit.
- The most competitive.
- It's no joke.
- What's more, - Nice one.
- when it comes to Incheon, - It comes naturally.
The city has...
- It's tough.
- Are you going for it, Jae Won?
- How chaotic.
- Are you calling it?
- Yes. Here I go.
- You are?
- You're going for it immediately?
- Go ahead.
It's fine.
- He's going for it right away.
- Can't I?
- No, you can.
- Go for it.
Do it when you've got it.
- Go with your instincts.
- The wheels could touch it.
- He's found the momentum.
- Do I push it?
- Do I?
- Don't shift the blame onto me.
You decide.
(Yo Han doesn't give rash advice.)
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 4.)
Is this it?
(4th try, Jae Won)
I'm sorry.
(Laughing)
(Comforting Jae Won)
- But Jae Won did well.
- After watching Jae Won...
on "Squid Game,"
I thought he was out of the ordinary...
and scary.
- But he's very gentle.
- I'll go.
- If you park there, - See that?
Others can't park properly.
That car should be towed.
(4th try, Yeon Seok)
Don't let it spin off.
He's got it.
- It's on the line.
- The car's out.
- The game is...
- Yo Han.
(Only two drivers are left.)
Hold on.
(4th try, Yo Han)
This is not easy at all.
(Nervous)
- When you push it...
- You can push it hard because...
- Yeon Seok's car will stop yours.
- It'll stop your car.
Yeon Seok's car will stop yours, so push hard.
Make a bold move.
(4th try, Yo Han)
(Coward Byun)
- Go bold...
- I told you to go bold.
- I tried going bold.
- Let's see.
Let's sweep...
(4th try, Jae Seok)
No.
You pulled it too much.
(They failed the fourth try.)
I'm going to practice for a bit.
That's enough. I get the sound now.
- See? I told you.
- Jae Won.
- I got your sound.
- I see.
- Wait.
- You've got it too, right?
Hold on. How did I...
I clearly started from here.
But Jae Won's car keeps curving to the right.
- Right?
- It curves slightly to the right.
- Okay.
- That was a good one.
- Okay, let's try.
- We'd better check...
the alignment of Jae Won's car.
(He burst out laughing at the car joke.)
Aren't I right, sir? The car needs an alignment check.
I know, right?
(Asking for a repair)
You can replace your car.
No, I'll go for it.
You're going for it?
(Jae Won suddenly declares that he'll give it a try.)
- Are you going for it?
- Why?
- Compared to your skills...
- He's stubborn.
Compared to your skills, you call out...
Listen. The more I do it,
- the more I feel...
- Do you improve?
Like I'm improving.
You're too daring for someone with your skills.
(Something he really wanted to say)
Are you ready? Are you going for it?
- Yes.
- Let's do it.
- Do we go 1st and 2nd?
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Go!
- Wait.
If I call it, can the next person not practice?
- No. Just do it.
- Then no.
- No, let's practice more.
- I'm going for it.
- Here I go.
- Here he goes.
- Go for it.
- I'm going for it.
I'm just going for it.
- Here I go.
- Yes, good luck.
Thank you.
(6th try, Yo Han)
Seriously!
What was that?
- Why scream?
- It's okay.
- It's fine. We can hit it in.
- Good.
- Yo Han.
- You can push it in.
- We can hit it in.
- Do it the way you did earlier.
I've got the hang of the sound.
That's enough.
(6th try, Jae Won)
- It's in.
- Nice.
- Nice!
- It's in!
- It's in.
- Nice.
(Cheering)
- Nice!
- It's in!
I told you, didn't I? I can tell just by hearing the sound.
I can tell by hearing the sound.
- I can tell by the sound.
- Well done.
- Was it just then?
- Yes, right then.
Imagine how happy he must've been.
- Should I try?
- Yes.
The alignment doesn't need a checkup.
(6th try, Yeon Seok)
(Park one more car, and they'll succeed.)
All good now.
- I'll park it there.
- Okay.
- I'll park my car there.
- Good.
- I'll park nice and clean.
- Okay.
I'm a military driver.
(6th try, Yeon Seok)
Parking? Come on.
It won't reach the line.
No, it was too much.
(What's the result?)
It was too much.
Nice. Good.
- It's stuck.
- The car went over.
It went over an inch too far.
(Jae Seok is the only driver left.)
Wait a minute.
Hey, Yeon Seok. You actually did well.
- Your car works as a stopper.
- Will it help?
You shouldn't go gently.
- No, I shouldn't.
- Go hard here.
(Fully wound)
Wind it too much, and both will fall off.
(Spinning)
(Laughing)
- I got nervous.
- That was too strong.
That just now was too much.
(6th try, Jae Seok)
I'm getting nervous myself.
I can't watch it. I'm getting nervous myself.
I could tell by Jae Won's sound earlier.
How about trying again?
No, just do it.
- Okay.
- Why not just push it?
But Yeon Seok's car is blocking the edge.
- You'll make it.
- I will.
It's in.
- It's in.
- It was weak.
- I should've pulled it back more.
- Failed.
(He's really bummed out.)
Failed.
Even the parked car doesn't count, right?
My mouth is drying up. I'm drinking a full bottle of water.
(Back to practicing)
- Nice.
- Good one.
- Just push it?
- Nice.
It's...
- Pushing it is...
- Good.
- Pulling it won't work.
- I'm succeeding in a row.
But why can't I do it during the game?
Calling it makes you all nervous.
Nobody is using the momentum, right?
Here I go. I'm going for it.
- What?
- I'm just going for it.
- Wait.
- Let us practice.
- These guys are...
- Here I go.
Why are these guys so impatient?
- Why are these guys so impatient?
(7th try, Yo Han)
He called it.
- He did.
- Push it in.
- We just have to push it in.
- Leave it there.
Just push it in.
(7th try, Jae Seok)
Let's do this.
Is it too much?
Go first.
(Self-maintenance)
- I've lost it.
- Yeon Seok should go.
Go ahead, Yeon Seok.
(7th try, Yeon Seok)
- I'm going to push the car in.
- Okay.
Let me open the doors.
That's a good idea.
(The goal is to push Yo Han's car in.)
I'd better push hard.
That's enough. No, it's too much.
You're pushing it in, right?
- No, Jae Seok. It won't go in.
- It's going in.
It's going in.
Okay. That's fine.
They could just hit both cars in.
Okay.
(Feeling even more pressure)
(There's a chance if Jae Seok hits hard.)
Just hit them.
(7th try, Jae Seok)
- That's quite hard.
- It is, but it's fine.
- Is it too much?
- Just hurry already.
- Just hit the cars.
- That's the goal, right?
Come on.
Oh, dear.
(It's the ace's turn.)
- That was...
- Jae Won could succeed.
Pull too much, and the car will curve.
- If you hit hard, - Right.
- the cars could go in.
- Don't use too much momentum.
(7th try, Jae Won)
Just push it with force.
Jae Won did well until now.
Whoosh.
Failed.
(Failed)
What did you say when you pushed the car?
(Whoosh)
I'm getting car sickness from all the tries.
But I really...
I'm not the only one getting car sickness.
- No.
- You get car sickness...
even when you're not in the car.
Interesting.
- Do you want to use the chance?
- Should we use the chance?
- Okay.
- Let's use the chance.
Here, sir.
One unlucky chance is mixed in them. Right.
- Please pick a good one.
- Okay.
(A valuable chance for the ninth try)
A bold move.
- An extra car.
- "An extra car for this try."
We get five cars in total.
- Nice.
- We have one more chance.
- Yes, nice.
- Nice.
- It was a good one.
Someone good should get the extra car.
You...
This is tough.
- Yo Han...
- We should take away Yo Han's car.
Yo Han...
You can't have the extra car.
Yo Han can't have the extra car.
- Can't someone get all the cars?
- Wait.
Can't someone get all the cars?
I so want to give my car to one person.
I can't control my strength.
Let me practice.
- Well done, Jae Won.
- Nice.
- Do you want the extra car?
- Another one, Jae Won?
- Okay.
- Okay, good.
The best driver.
Let's do a group cheer.
- We must succeed on this try.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Go!
Let's succeed Round Two.
We have an extra car for this round.
- I'll leave it here.
- Should I go first?
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 9.)
(Chance: An extra car, 9th try, Jae Seok)
- It's going in.
- Nice one.
Come on.
Seriously.
I'll park safely.
(Chance: An extra car, 9th try, Yeon Seok)
- Nice.
- It's going in.
- That was close.
- All right.
- Come here.
- I'm sorry.
- You can do it.
- Jae Won.
- We have an extra car.
- Okay.
- I'll go.
(Chance: An extra car, 9th try, Jae Won)
- Go.
- It's going in.
It's in.
- Go.
- It's going in.
- It's in.
(It's in!)
Okay, Yo Han's turn.
- We have an extra car.
- Jae Won, do the last car.
- Okay.
Don't get excited.
Stay calm.
I want to cry.
Good luck, Namdong.
(Chance: An extra car, 9th try, Yo Han)
(Only one more car needs to be parked.)
It's going in.
- Jae Won.
- If I push out the car...
that's parked inside, it's a fail, right?
Correct.
(A highly challenging parking setup)
I think I can succeed.
(I think I can succeed.)
Don't waver. Use your own method.
Trust yourself.
(Chance: An extra car, 9th try, Jae Won)
Okay, I'll trust myself.
- I'm not going for it.
- What?
- It's a try if you go for it.
- You're using the chance.
Sorry?
There's no practice.
- We're on the 9th try.
- This is the 9th try.
You're nervous, aren't you?
(Unable to pull himself together)
Jae Won.
- You can do it!
- I can do it.
(Being careful)
You can do it, Jae Won.
Pull it off, and you're safely parked.
- Okay.
- No pressure.
You can do it. You'll definitely do it.
It's going in.
I'm sorry.
Failed.
We have to succeed.
- It's our last try.
- Is it our last try?
Yes, it is.
- We have to succeed for them.
- I'm going crazy.
We have to give them the presents.
- We have to get them the presents.
- Hold on.
(They only have one chance now.)
Hold on.
If I do this, it'll be too strong.
- Let's try it now.
- Okay.
Now, this is the last chance.
I didn't know we'd end up here in Round Two.
I'm sorry, but since it's the last try...
- Please decide the order for us.
- No, that's not it.
Let's chant, "Go, Namdong Best Drivers."
"Namdong Best Drivers."
He's going for some PR now.
- It's the last chance anyway.
- He wants to be the next chairman.
One, two...
- Go, Namdong Best Drivers.
Right. He asked for it because we were likely to fail.
Yes.
- Let's do this!
- Yes.
- Here we go.
- Go, Namdong Best Drivers.
- Are you going for it?
- Yes. Here I go.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on the last try.)
Gosh. I didn't expect to be here in Round Two...
after succeeding on our first try.
(Last try, Jae Won)
Goodness.
(He misses by a hair.)
(Last try, Jae Won)
- Excuse me.
- Gosh.
- Don't think about that one.
- Okay.
- Don't think about it.
- It's better because it's blocking.
- Right.
(Last try, Yo Han)
- I'll get one, at least.
- Do it.
(Last try, Yeon Seok)
- I'll get one, at least.
- Do it.
(Last try, Yeon Seok)
That one is there.
Go, Namdong Best Drivers.
- Go!
(They have to park it this time.)
Nice.
(Move.)
(Last try, Jae Seok)
What do I do to make a miracle happen?
(They need a miraculous shot.)
(Last try, Jae Seok)
When you hit this one,
this one can go and push this one.
(Last try, Jae Seok)
- Let's try that.
- Try hitting this one first.
- You have to hit that one.
- That's the only way.
I have to hit that one.
Let's go.
You never know.
(Failed overall)
(Retrieving the presents)
- Good job.
- Well done.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
- Good job. No.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay.
We blew nine chances.
It's hard.
You're right. It's very hard.
The middle is...
This isn't enough, but...
- Thanks.
- Sorry.
- No.
- We should've won the presents.
My wife wanted this the most.
(Squeezing his eyes shut)
I wish Namdong Best Drivers the best.
Okay.
(Wrapping up the first spare time with not-the-best results)
Gosh. What a shame.
- No, it's okay.
- Just buy the presents.
Gosh. It's a shame, though.
I'm so disappointed.
We succeeded on our 1st try in Round 1.
What's done is done.
- We'll do better in Round Two.
- Yes.
What is the time that we meet our next client?
What time?
We should've succeeded before meeting the next one.
It's at 2:30pm.
- Then we'll eat first.
- Yes. We should eat first.
I wanted to succeed...
and proudly go to a diner for drivers.
It was on the tip of my tongue, but I held it back.
When you ask taxi drivers,
they'll tell you the great spots right away.
Why don't we ask for a good spot to eat to...
- Let's ask...
- It's tough, though.
- Should I ask them?
- Who?
Should I ask them?
Now?
That's a bit...
Let's play rock-paper-scissors, and the loser will ask them.
I think I can play rock-paper-scissors.
- They do know the good spots.
- Okay.
They know all the great spots to eat.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Win, win, lose, lose)
- Scissors.
(It's a tie.)
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Scissors.
(Lost)
(Hurray!)
- Hey, go and ask them.
- Let's go, Yeon Seok.
They'll tell you.
- Good job.
- It's a shame.
It's a shame, indeed. But well done.
- Okay.
- Thanks for coming.
(Uneasy)
Please stay healthy. Thanks for everything.
- Thank you.
- Goodness.
- I wish you good health.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Yes. Please stay healthy.
- I'll look forward to it.
- Okay.
- I'll prepare it well.
- Thank you.
- Gosh.
Sorry.
- I've been enjoying your work.
- Gosh. Okay.
Yes.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
(Frustrated)
Is there a good spot to eat around here?
Yeon Seok wants to ask you...
which restaurant is good near here.
- A diner.
- You might know the place.
There's a sushi place in front of the city hall.
- A sushi place?
- They sell udon too.
I thought you'd tell us a diner for drivers.
- Is their udon good?
- Yes, it is.
Got it.
- That spot is good.
- Okay. It's in Guwol-dong.
If you'll be driving the cab, sir...
Do you want me to get you there?
Or do you want our chairman's car?
- No, it's okay.
- I can...
- Thank you.
- No. I can drive you there.
- Hop in.
- What's wrong with you?
- What's gotten into you?
You'll pay the fare, won't you?
- Of course.
- Yes.
- We'll pay the fare.
- Of course.
- That's...
- Then it's all right, isn't it?
- You're shameless.
- We'll pay the fare.
- Yes.
- I know.
- Then it's fine.
- Yes.
- I know.
We'll pay the fare.
- Thank you.
Still...
- Jae Seok.
- You can sit in the front.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Sir, it's because...
If he's going to drive the cab anyway,
- I know.
- you know...
- I actually wanted to try it.
- Exactly.
Hello.
Thank you.
- I'm sorry, sir.
- No, it's all right.
Thank you. Really.
- Thank you for your kindness.
- It's good.
- Please turn on the taxi meter.
- Okay.
Are we going to the sushi spot...
- he recommended?
- Yes. That sushi spot.
- Is there another place to eat?
- There's a Korean set meal place.
- That sounds good.
- Where is it?
- It's in Mansu-dong.
- How does that sound?
- Sounds good.
- Sounds great.
- Let's go to that place.
- Okay. Got it.
- Do you go there often?
- Yes. I go there often.
I see.
Gosh. This is nice.
(Looking around)
The car is so neat and tidy inside.
- I know.
- It's very well managed.
- It's your workplace in a way.
- Yes.
How long do you drive a day?
When it's a long day, I drive for 15 hours.
- Gosh.
- It goes up to 16 hours sometimes.
That's a super long day.
- Usually, it's 10 to 12 hours.
- Gosh. How?
I think that's our regular hours.
You have to take good care...
- of your back.
- Yes.
You're entering a school zone.
When Jae Won pulled it off,
he threw his arms up like a child at school.
- I know. That was exhilarating.
- It's a shame.
- It is.
It's not easy.
When I watched Whenever Possible,
I wondered how I'd feel after I failed.
I felt pressured.
How do you feel?
Gosh.
- It's really...
- It's lousy, doesn't it?
It doesn't feel good at all.
On top of feeling so sorry for them,
I don't feel good at all.
It's not a good feeling.
- I don't feel good.
- It sucks.
I'll see toy taxis on the ceiling when I'm in bed tonight.
I know. I'll see them too.
- There are some restaurants here.
- Yes.
There's a 24-hour restaurant over there.
Is that it? I see.
You can drop us off here.
- Thank you.
- Please stay healthy.
- It's okay.
- Okay.
- Sir, drive safely.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Okay. Good luck.
Gosh. It smells good already.
It looks like a great restaurant.
- Shall we go inside?
- Yes.
- Go to the table in the center.
- Okay.
Gosh. Hello.
Hey. Their doenjang stew is only eight dollars.
- It's all under 10 dollars.
- Nothing is under 10 dollars...
- in Seoul.
- A set meal is seven dollars.
- Let's order stir-fried spicy pork.
- That sounds good.
Let's get stir-fried spicy pork, kongbiji stew, and...
- Let's order a budae stew too.
- Yes.
- Ttukbaegi bulgogi sounds nice.
- That sounds good.
- Let's share tofu and kimchi too.
- Let's do that.
It's a feast.
Good.
Do you have siblings, Jae Won?
I have a younger sister.
- A younger sister.
- Yes.
- She's like a close friend.
- Is she like a friend?
She's seven years younger than me, but we're like friends.
She plays the guitar.
- Really?
- Is she a musician?
She wants to be. So she performs and all.
Do you go to her performances when you're invited?
I've seen her perform once.
That's cool. It's an artist family.
What about you, Yo Han?
I have a younger sister who is a year younger than me.
Is she a year younger than you? What is she like?
Now that we're old enough, we're like friends too.
We're comfortable around each other.
You all have younger sisters.
We all have younger sisters.
By the way, I have two younger sisters.
I've always talked from my point of view.
But when I see myself in my sisters' perspectives,
I'm such a lousy brother.
- Why?
- Listen.
I'm a bad brother.
Unlike Yo Han and Jae Won,
- I wasn't sweet to them.
- You weren't like a friend to them?
- No.
- No?
The two sisters were close to each other.
- They weren't close to you.
- No.
I tried it a few times,
- but they blocked me out.
- I see.
I wasn't sweet like,
"Hey, sister. Hey, brother." It wasn't like that.
I teased her.
- That's nothing.
- I messed with her.
That means you were very close.
I think my sister will laugh when she sees this.
What?
- Is that a wedding band?
- Yes.
Gosh. You're flashing it.
- I'm married.
- What?
- I'm a married man.
- "I'm a married man."
- Is it Tiffany's?
- Yes, it is.
- Gosh.
- Is it really Tiffany's?
- Yes.
- Because she's Tiffany?
- It's because she's Tiffany.
- Yes.
- Gosh. I was just asking him.
- Goodness.
Really.
- Tiffany's Tiffany.
- Yes. Tiffany and Tiffany.
How's life as a newlywed?
I like it.
She's a better person than I am.
- Tiffany is.
- Yes.
I've changed a lot.
You can't help but change when you're married.
- It's here.
- Thank you.
Gosh. It looks good.
- Gosh. Thanks.
- Ttukbaegi bulgogi.
- Look at the side dishes.
- There are a lot.
It's here.
Gosh. Look at that budae stew. It's only nine dollars.
(Kongbiji stew)
It's big.
- Thanks for the food.
- Enjoy.
(The table is full of food.)
Give it to me.
Gosh, Jae Won. I love it.
(The youngest laddles the stew for the older brothers.)
I love it.
- I'll give you a little for now.
- Okay.
It's tasty.
(Slurping)
Gosh. It's good.
(Yo Han also tries the noodles first.)
I'm glad we ordered the stir-fried spicy pork.
Gosh. It's good. It's really tasty.
(Yeon Seok devours budae stew too.)
- It's delicious.
- Kongbiji stew is so good.
- Is it good?
- Yes, it's very good.
- It's light.
- Yes.
- Gosh. I love it.
- It's delicious.
We can order more noodles if we want more.
- We have to add more noodles.
- Ma'am, we'll get more noodles.
- More noodles?
- Yes. Thank you.
Do you want me to ladle the kongbiji stew for you?
But I don't have a bowl.
Sir.
Sir, can we get four more bowls?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
(Laughing)
I craved this kind of food.
I see.
(Chowing down the spicy pork wrapped in lettuce)
It's so cheap.
(He's amazed again by how cheap it is.)
Incheon people are warm-hearted.
That's right. Sure.
They're filled with love.
You can't go wrong with the driver's recommendation.
- Let's have our protein.
- Let's do our best.
- Yes.
- Let's get it done.
Yes.
To pay for lunch,
- Let's do it.
- we'll play a game.
- No.
- Are you going to have coffee?
- What?
- Coffee.
- Shall we?
- Let's add coffee to lunch.
Sounds good.
Are you doubling the bet already...
- "Double it."
- at this place?
- Let's add coffee to the bet.
- Here?
- Sounds good.
- What game should we play?
Let's flip a coin and guess heads or tails.
That one's fun.
Shall we?
If only one person gets a different one...
I see. Heads or tails.
- Okay.
- Sounds good.
If three people got heads,
- the one with the tails pays. Good.
- Yes.
(Paying for lunch)
- Lastly...
- I mean, I enjoyed the food.
Now that we have...
- The sharks are here.
- Exactly.
We should try it.
(Whose money are they going to use?)
- It's Admiral Yi Sun Sin or 100.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Who's going first?
- Let's do it together.
- Together?
- At the same time.
- In 1, 2, 3.
(Shaking)
Don't flip it. Do it as is.
- One...
- Hold on. Let's gather our hands.
One...
- One...
- Excuse me.
- Sorry.
- He's onto something.
- Hold on. You're using a trick.
- I didn't see it.
- Hold on.
- I almost fell.
- Why do you use a trick here?
I think he used a trick. Let's reveal it one by one.
One by one.
(Nervous)
Let's start with Jae Won.
(Jae Won, who got caught using a trick, goes first.)
Heads.
(Roh Jae Won, heads)
(You go first. No, you go first.)
Here I go.
(In the end, Yeon Seok goes first.)
(Yoo Yeon Seok, tails)
Tails. It's 1-to-1.
(Tails 1 versus Heads 1)
- It's 1-to-1.
- Tails.
- Goodness.
(Jae Seok goes next.)
- What?
- Okay. Heads.
(Yu Jae Seok, heads)
Hold on.
(Tails 1 versus Heads 2)
(Yo Han reveals it last.)
(Yo Han, heads)
(Yeon Seok has to pay.)
(Wailing)
(Happy inside)
(Happy outside)
Be quiet.
- Let's keep quiet.
- Thanks, Yeon Seok.
Thanks for the food, Yeon Shik.
(He lost the rock-paper-scissors before too.)
Yeon Shik, you have to buy coffee too.
It's amazing how the one who asked for a game gets picked.
Yeon Shik will pay for the food and coffee.
Thank you.
It's been a while since he treated me.
We enjoyed the food, Yeon Seok.
Thank you.
- We enjoyed the food.
- Okay.
- Thanks, Yeon Seok.
- Thank you.
- I got played by the sharks.
- Bye.
(Current time, 1:55pm)
Isn't it hot, Yo Han?
I'm all right. I came back from Hawaii yesterday.
- This is nothing.
- Are you all right?
I hate feeling hot.
- You don't like the heat?
- I hate the heat.
We don't have time to drink coffee.
- Let's go to the spare time spot.
- First, let's go to...
But he's supposed to buy us coffee.
By the way, it was extra delicious because you bought it.
- I don't know why. When you pay, - By the way,
- it's more delicious.
- I had such good food...
- after a while.
- Right?
The food itself was tasty,
but it tasted so much better because you paid for it.
(Reviewing the experience excitedly)
Should we get coffee from the mart if we don't have time?
- Yes, we should.
- Here?
- Yes, let's get it here.
- Sure.
- We'll get it at the mart.
- You can get what you want.
- Yes, that's better.
- Yes.
- Good afternoon.
- Goodness.
- Hello.
- Gosh.
- I can't believe it.
- Good afternoon.
It's Yu Jae Seok.
Gosh. This place is quite big.
(They all head to the coffee section in a row.)
I'll get some for our staff too.
- How many are there?
- They should drink it too.
I'm so happy because Ahn Yeon Seok is buying everything.
- What are you getting?
- Should we mix up...
sweetened and unsweetened ones?
They have lattes too.
(Yeon Seok, a big spender, grabs lots of things.)
I'm so happy today.
(Yo Han chooses his quickly.)
Did you choose yours?
- Are we done now?
- Yes.
- Have you all chosen yours?
Then I'll get...
(He hasn't chosen yet.)
I'll get the barley tea.
- Or black barley tea?
- Is it enough for our staff?
Korean raisin tea?
How many are you?
(He still couldn't pick water.)
(He noticed something.)
You're here. Drink this one.
That's Jae Seok.
- I'll drink this one, then.
- Have that one.
I'll get this one.
He said I was on here.
- He knows what's up. Look.
- I knew it.
He said I was here.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- This way, please.
- Hello.
Hi.
- Yes.
- Aren't we getting snacks?
This is a bundle of two.
(He wants it.)
Okay. Get it.
The chocolate flavor is better, though.
- Yes.
- Right?
(He gets a chocolate snack with Yeon Shik's permission.)
You're here again.
(Suggesting buying a box)
Gosh. Come on. I'm good with the drink.
(The model, Jae Seok, is happy.)
- It's 25.90 dollars.
- Okay.
(It's yours, Jae Seok.)
(Satisfied)
- Thank you.
- Have a good day. Thanks.
- Have a good day.
- Let's have a packet.
- Yes.
(They enjoy the snack as soon as they bought it.)
Turn left.
- You know where it is, right?
- Yes.
(Wiping off the sweat)
Gosh. It's hot.
(Clicking his tongue)
(They worry about one friend as it gets hotter.)
- Hey, Yo Han.
- Yes.
Your leather jacket.
It must be hot.
- I'm good.
- Really?
- Even if you're back from Hawaii...
- Don't worry about me.
Even if you're back from Hawaii...
I mean, it's hot wearing short sleeves right now.
I'm not going to take the jacket off until we're finished.
Good.
I'm going to keep being loyal until the end.
(Son of Incheon is persistent.)
We need to take Bus 56 here.
(They've arrived at the bus stop while keeping the jacket on.)
You like it, don't you?
This is one of my favorite snacks.
- You love sweets.
- I love them.
- It's good.
- Gosh. You're so sweaty.
Is it your jacket? Or are you feeling unwell?
(Laughing)
Are you going to faint?
- Don't mind me even if I faint.
- Here.
Please do not mind me even if I black out.
- I'll take control of myself.
- You'll get dehydrated.
I'm worried you'll faint from dehydration...
when we have to play a game.
I'll handle it myself.
- I'm worried if you'll be okay.
- It's hot indeed.
You know what I'm wearing this.
The "Tazza" poster is red.
(The color of the "Tazza" poster is red.)
I can't take it off.
You could've worn something thin in red.
Gosh. The fabric is so thick.
Really. It's suede.
(His passionate self won't give up the suede under the blazing sun.)
It's okay.
- I'll be determined until the end.
- Okay.
- That's it.
- It's here. We have to catch it.
Hello, sir.
- Good afternoon.
- Thanks.
- Yes.
- Gosh. It feels so much better.
- Right?
- Can I turn the AC on for me?
- Yes. Just one, though.
- You can't keep two.
- Do you want to sit here?
- Just a little bit.
- Sit here.
It feels much better.
You look cool, though.
Fashionistas don't take off their clothes.
- Is that so?
- You know it.
- I'll keep it until the end.
- Okay.
What's your MBTI, Jae Won?
- I'm an INFP.
- I see. An INFP.
You're an INFP. Yes.
- What about you?
- I'm an ISFP.
I'm the lazy type.
- Are you not a planner, then?
- Not at all.
- Do you plan things?
- I don't.
- You're not a planner either.
- No.
- What about you?
- I make plans subtly.
I've never planned anything in life.
Is it "Carpe diem," then?
Do you appreciate every moment?
I don't appreciate it.
- What do you do, then?
- I just...
What do you do, then?
Don't you know what I do? I work like this.
I just do what I'm supposed to do.
Yu Jae Seok is shooting something.
He's on the bus.
- What?
- They're on the bus together.
What is it?
- I'm a fan, Jae Seok.
- Who?
Someone reported this to the radio.
They're talking about us.
- This is crazy.
- How are we on the radio?
Isn't this the first time ever?
What's happening?
- A passenger must've texted it.
- Did they?
(A passenger on the same bus told the radio station right away.)
Incheon people are so kind.
- Incheon people are full of love.
- I love them.
They send the story out right after encountering us.
In Incheon,
they embrace us.
It's charming, isn't it? When we get off,
it'll be very artistic.
- It's the Culture and Arts Center.
- The Culture and Arts Center.
- We need to go further.
- I think it's the next stop.
- You're right.
- Right?
- It's from Jang Woo Shik.
- Woo Shik.
"Every day, I stand at the very back of the 100 people,"
"and I lead the 1-hour-and-30-minute march..."
"with a thump after a thump."
"With a gesture light as a feather, I roar like thunder..."
"while securing the same spot for 20 years."
"Dear Whenever Possible, please be my first movement today."
- I see. He's a musician.
- He plays an instrument or music.
At the back,
(Is the second Whenever Guest a musician who plays an instrument?)
- he might play the bass drum.
- The bass drum. Right.
- That was entertaining to watch.
- It's very dynamic.
- Incheon is very dynamic.
- It's great.
Living here is a rollercoaster ride.
It's different from day to day.
(Incheon is never boring.)
Hold on.
Do you even know where you're going?
Where is it? Tell us.
Hold on.
- I like it.
- This place is lovely.
It's nice and cool.
Try it.
Should I try this one?
(He smoothly joins him.)
My lower back. Gosh.
(Standing up)
I can't do it. I'll get sweaty.
He'll get sweaty.
- We have to go to the west gate.
- The west gate?
- Is it this way?
- Yes.
Gosh. Since it's a large region, I can't tell where I'm at.
(Glancing)
Jae Won is always so quiet...
and walks two steps behind.
It's hard to squeeze myself between you to be in the frame.
- It feels...
- Come on.
- he's two steps behind us.
- Stop going behind us.
- Why are you always behind us?
- Walk in front of us.
(Bravely leading the group)
- Let's go this way, Jae Won.
- Okay.
Hey, it's the west gate.
This is the west gate.
(They've arrived at the second spare time spot, )
(Incheon Culture and Arts Center.)
Gosh. It's hot.
(Enter the west gate and come all the way down the left hallway.)
Good afternoon. Hi.
- We have to turn left...
- It's all the way down, right?
And go all the way down.
- What? Good afternoon.
- Hello.
- Woo Shik?
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
- Gosh. Good afternoon.
- Good afternoon.
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you. Gosh.
- Nice to meet you too.
(Whenever Guest is waiting for them at the end of the hallway.)
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
Is this the Incheon Philharmonic Orchestra?
Yes, it's the Incheon Metropolitan City Arts Troupe.
The Incheon Metropolitan City Arts Troupe.
My favorite actors are here.
- Gosh.
- Really.
- Let's go inside and talk.
- Yes. Follow me.
- It's a bit confusing in here.
- I see.
The practice room for the orchestra is on the left.
- Is it here?
- Yes.
(He's a member of the Incheon Philharmonic Orchestra.)
Please come this way.
- Hello.
- Gosh. It's nice and cold.
It's cold, right?
(The practice room is big and pleasant.)
Gosh. I feel better now.
Gosh. It's so cool.
The percussionists sit here.
I mainly play the timpani.
- Goodness.
- The timpani.
(Usually, the practice room for the Incheon Philharmonic...)
(is filled with music.)
(Including violins, )
(cellos, )
(and horns, )
(various instruments create a harmony.)
(What makes the rumbling sound at the very back...)
(is Whenever Guest Woo Shik's timpani.)
(Rumbling)
(A deep, resonant sound that brings all sounds together)
(Timpani, the heart of an orchestra)
You are indeed at the very back.
Yes. Most of the time,
I stand face-to-face with the conductor.
- Will you play for us?
- Yes.
(Rumbling)
(Surprised)
(The magnificent sound fills up the huge practice room.)
(Amazed)
(Controlling its pitch with a pedal)
(They can't help but clap.)
Awesome.
That was awesome.
- It rolled.
- Yes.
(Timpani's magnificent charms)
Gosh. It was so cool.
- Yes.
- Let's go that way.
- At the percussion section, - Look at the bass drum.
- we have drums.
- It's a percussion section.
- There's a cymbal too.
- There are pedals.
This is a marimba.
Yes. This instrument is called a marimba.
(Jae Seok notices the marimba.)
I don't usually play it.
You don't, but...
(Amazed)
It sounds so pretty.
It has such a beautiful sound.
(Its beautiful sound makes them focus.)
(Darn it.)
(He made a mistake because it has been a while.)
"Darn it."
- Anyway, let's sit and talk.
- Yes.
(Looking around)
I didn't expect Yo Han to come.
Nice to meet you. I performed in a play here.
- Really?
- Here?
- When I was in middle school.
- I see.
- Son of Incheon came here.
Anyway, we're here to visit the orchestra.
Is the practice usually over by this time?
Today, we were done a bit early.
Usually, we practice from 10am to 3pm.
- Those are the practice hours.
- Yes.
There are so many different instruments.
Why did you choose percussion?
I had to go to college when I was a high school student.
I studied hard in my sophomore year, but I wasn't good at it.
Fortunately, my older sister was majoring in percussion.
- She played the instrument.
- Yes.
For other instruments,
- you have to have your own.
- Right.
But as for percussion, you can share the instruments.
That's why I majored it with her.
(He even went to Germany to study percussion.)
I started when I was 17, so it's been 36 years.
(He played the timpani for 36 years, now as a member of the orchestra.)
That's amazing.
I'm sorry,
but how much is the timpani?
I know the Incheon Philharmonic's timpani is over 100,000 dollars.
And 1 set is consists of 5.
Gosh. That's...
Practicing it must be intimidating.
- Gosh. It's so expensive.
- Yes.
I'm treating it with great care.
Percussion instruments tend to be expensive.
The name of the instrument reminds me of...
- Today, it keeps popping up.
- It sounds familiar.
That's the vibe of today.
We came to Guwol-dong when it's September.
- Timpani and Tiffany.
(Timpani, Tiffany)
We are rhyming like crazy today.
Everything fits perfectly, except for the weather.
It's so hot today.
I played the drums before.
- Yes.
- I saw it in the drama.
Yes. Compared to other instruments, it's more noticeable...
when you make a mistake when you play the percussion.
Of course.
Have you ever made mistakes while performing?
- Have you made mistakes?
- Yes.
It's going to be tough talking about it.
I'm still traumatized by it.
What happened?
Maestro Gum was conducting the orchestra.
- Maestro Gum Nanse.
Toward the end of the song, I played the timpani.
It was supposed to go slowly as the piece went by.
Da-da-da.
(After slowing down, he had to strike it to finish.)
I'd strike it hard after playing the timpani.
I was supposed to look at the maestro.
I just thought, "Why are we slowing down so much?"
"Yes, this is about the time." And I slammed it.
But the maestro's hand was still up here.
I slammed it, then it was followed by others.
- You had a head start.
- Yes.
- At that time...
- What happened?
- I came to see him.
- I see.
And he said, "I dragged a bit, didn't I?"
Are you doing an impression of him?
(Laughing)
I've never seen an impression of Maestro Gum.
He has a unique way of speaking.
If you like it, then it's fine.
(He loves it.)
Well, since you're playing the percussion,
do you have any occupational habits?
Gosh. My occupational habits.
When I walk on the streets,
I don't just walk, I split the beat.
- I see.
- You split the rhythm.
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three.
One, and two, and three.
One, ta-ta, two, ta-ta, three, ta-ta.
I split the beats like that.
Before a drama begins, there's a countdown...
on the screen.
I go like this, "One, and two, and..."
- Also with the turn signal.
- It's all about beats.
You always think about the beat.
Yes. That's what I do.
(He's always obsessed with the beat.)
By the way, what made you...
send the letter to us?
I love watching TV so much.
- Really?
- I love dramas and variety shows.
I'm always watching TV during my break...
- if I'm not studying.
- You're a TV aficionado.
- Yes.
- I see.
I was watching Whenever Possible,
and I thought, "Will I be able to do that?"
And at the end, the caption appeared...
for those who want to wend the letter.
- At the bottom.
- Yes.
So, I wrote the letter about two years ago.
(2 years ago?)
- Really?
- Two years ago?
It must be surprising to get the call after two years.
I hung up because it was from a number I didn't know.
- You thought it was a prank.
- Yes.
Then I got a text right away.
So, I called at once.
You are full of fun stories.
Am I?
Anyway, now that we're here...
in Guwol-dong,
- I want to wrap it up nicely.
- Yes, we should.
Sons of Incheon,
- Yo Han and Jae Won, are here.
- Two Sons of Incheon.
We have to make up for the previous mistakes.
Now, Round One.
"An item to take care of the timpani..."
"with which I perform 60 times a year."
"A dehumidifier from the LG Objet Collection."
- Nice. A dehumidifier.
- That's a nice one.
Gosh. A dehumidifier.
Gosh. That's a nice one.
(LG dehumidifier to keep the timpani nice and dry)
What is that game?
(Approaching)
- Let's try it.
- They're placing it...
Can I try it?
Of course. Feel free to try it.
- Thank you.
- It's okay.
Jae Won must be trying it out.
It was bought with the taxes of Incheon citizens.
- He's from Incheon.
- He's an Incheon citizen.
He still lives in Incheon.
- Really?
- It was bought with the taxes.
You should try playing it.
You must've played a bit of piano.
(Chuckling)
Do you still play the drums?
(What is this mission with Jae Won's marimba?)
(Music Stand Pong!)
(The table tennis ball is bounced...)
(to remove all balls on the music stand.)
(Round 1, target goal, 4)
We have to bounce the ball to knock off the other balls.
(Target)
- We must bounce it once, right?
- Yes.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Okay.
- The 4 of us get 1 ball each?
- Right.
- There's no time limit?
- There is a time limit.
- There's a time limit?
- It's 20 seconds.
- Okay.
These games are our expertise.
(With the tennis balls, )
(they threw them, )
(smashed them, )
(blew them, )
(and put them in.)
(They've tried all kinds of games with the table tennis balls.)
(Table tennis ball game master)
- We should practice.
- Let's practice.
- It's tough when one ball is left.
- Right.
(The table tennis ball master steps up first.)
I should feel its bounce.
(I should feel its bounce.)
- Gosh.
- What if this happens?
All of the balls must be removed.
- What?
- I see.
- All of the balls must be removed.
All of the balls must be removed.
(All of the balls?)
- Gosh.
(Failing again)
This is looking bad, Yeon Shik.
- Yeon Shik.
- A bit weaker.
- Hold on!
- Yeon Shik!
- A bit weaker.
- You should...
What?
It's hard.
Your aim was a bit off.
Darn it.
(Feeling embarrassed)
It's hard when there's one ball left.
- Right.
- One ball left.
Right.
It's hard when there's one ball left.
(Their shot percentage isn't that stable yet.)
But if that happens...
I hope we can win the dehumidifier.
Let's stop after Round One.
- Okay.
- It rolls off like this.
(I got it.)
Done.
We can pass Round One.
- Let's go for it.
- The four of us...
- Did you practice, Jae Won?
- Yes.
Actually, I don't feel confident.
- Let's give it a try.
You should go first.
- Let's do a cheer.
- One, two, three.
- Let's go!
- Let's go! Let's do this.
- You get 20 seconds.
- All right.
Here we go!
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
(1st try)
Nice.
- He got two at once.
- Let's go!
(Clear!)
(Laughing)
(Cheering)
(His eyes open wide as they pass right away.)
Gosh, we did this at once!
(They pass Round 1 at once.)
(Jae Won knocks off one ball.)
(Jae Seok gets 2 in 1 go.)
(Yo Han finishes it up.)
Round One, success!
- But Round One...
- This happened earlier.
- We have to stay focused.
- Right.
(Smiling)
- Don't get too excited.
- We shouldn't feel too happy.
- Earlier.
- This happened earlier.
We can get hurt when we get too excited.
- All right.
- Okay.
Don't be careless.
(Don't be careless.)
For the previous group, we passed Round One right away.
We couldn't pass Round Two after that.
- You'll make it.
- Let's stay calm.
It's okay. Go!
It's a go.
- All right. We did well.
- Hold on.
All right. Let's do well.
A one-day coffee truck for the 100 members of...
the Incheon Philharmonic Orchestra who march every day.
(Round 2 present, one-day coffee truck)
(Impressed)
A coffee truck!
(A one-day coffee truck for the Incheon Philharmonic Orchestra)
It says, "A treat from the timpani player!"
It will actually have this on top?
(The timpani player loves it.)
It looks like "Tiffany" from afar.
(Tiffany's husband will make it happen.)
(Round 2)
(There will be 2 more balls.)
(The row in front has 2 more balls.)
This will make it too hard.
(This is interesting.)
- This will make it too hard.
- We should practice.
- They're from the "Tazza" team.
- Right.
I'm sure they'll knock off two at once.
- This will make it too hard.
- Can we practice?
- Give it a try.
- What about the order?
Do you want to go last since you're doing well?
- Gosh, this is...
- Okay.
The ones at the start...
The ones at the start must do well.
They have to break up the balls.
Gosh.
Stop practicing.
I didn't get a single ball.
Okay.
What's wrong with me?
(Flustered)
(The master appears.)
Oh, good!
- Okay! Nice!
- We only have one ball each.
(I got it.)
It works when I sort of push it.
- How?
- Don't bounce it normally.
- Try to push it more.
- Like this?
- Right.
- That was too strong.
Don't bounce it. Try to push it.
I should keep this.
Nice!
There we go.
- Done.
- Jae Won should give it a try.
(The older ones have totally got the hang of it.)
That was nice.
(He steps up after the older ones are done practicing.)
Why would you throw it when there are no balls?
Don't get nervous.
Push it!
- Right.
- Push it!
- Nice!
There you go. You got it, right?
You shot it like a bullet.
Push it like this.
(He learns the bullet method.)
You got it, right?
Let's win them the coffee truck.
Good shot!
(There's hope for the coffee truck.)
Let's do a cheer.
One, two, three.
- Let's go!
- Are you going to play it for us?
- Yes.
Right.
(They get a burst of energy from the Whenever Guest.)
- Here we go!
- All right! Let's go!
- Go!
I feel nervous. Okay. Let's go!
Ready. Set.
- I'll be going second.
- Set.
(2nd try)
It's okay.
But it hit the ball.
(Sighing)
Gosh!
(2nd try)
- Gosh.
- Gosh. This is hard.
Gosh. This is hard.
- We shouldn't be careless.
- Each person should knock off one.
Let's go again.
- All right.
- Let's go again.
Hold on.
The tune at the start was a bit...
Play something bold for us.
- Bold?
- Right.
Gosh.
Got it.
(He goes on a journey for a bold sound.)
(The camera follows after him as well.)
"Thump!"
Shall we start?
This is our third try.
(He roots for their success with a bold sound.)
Here we go!
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 3.)
Ready. Set.
(3rd try)
- Nice!
- I only got one.
Nice.
I should've knocked off more than one.
Gosh!
That's the worst situation.
(Yo Han's shot is all that they can rely on!)
Gosh.
- Five, four...
- Go for the middle.
One person should get at least two.
- We should find a way.
- One person should get two.
Hold on.
The balls split up too much.
I'm starting to think that we don't have to throw it like this.
Hold on.
That wasn't it. Hold on.
You're planning to break the balls from up top, right?
He's trying to break them up from the top.
One person should do that.
Okay. Nice.
Using the vibration might be a method.
How about throwing four at once?
- Let's do it at the same time.
- At the same time?
- Let's give it a try.
Get ready.
One person should strike from above.
One person should strike from below.
What if we get in each other's way?
- Hey, Yo Han.
- Let's practice.
The smell of suede is so strong.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm starting to sweat again.
Let's do it again.
(The suede man is feeling very nervous.)
- One...
- One, two, three.
Gosh.
- This won't work.
This won't work.
- You should go first, Yeon Shik.
- No.
- I'll go first.
- You go first.
- We'll give it a try.
- Gosh.
Should I go second? Will you go second?
- I'll start.
- You should go second.
- Please call out, "Here we go."
- You go next.
- Here we go!
- Ready. Set.
(4th try)
- Hey!
- Gosh.
- Nice!
- This side.
There's a chance.
Nice!
This method is needed for this one.
- Slam it down!
- Do it on your own!
- We don't have time!
- We don't have time! Slam it!
- Go for it, Jae Won!
- Slam it!
Three...
(Aimless bullet)
Gosh!
Gosh.
(Failing miserably)
- Gosh!
- Don't slam it there!
(We told you not to get nervous.)
- I'm sorry.
- That can happen.
- Jae Won!
- I'm sorry.
This guy...
- Gosh.
- gets so nervous.
This was what I meant when I told you to slam it!
Okay.
We're trapped in a swamp right now.
Gosh.
Right.
It would be great to give everyone a cup of coffee.
- Even this was put together.
- Right.
Right. It shouldn't be too strong.
We should aim low.
Right.
- Right. Aim low.
- Nice.
- Let's go!
Here we go!
Ready. Set.
(6th try)
(He misses again.)
Gosh!
My gosh.
Five, four,
- Use a lot of strength.
- three, two...
(Fail)
- I'm sorry.
- It's fine.
(He returns with disappointment.)
I'm sorry, Jae Won.
- I'm sorry.
- Gosh.
- Jae Won...
- I broke down after seeing him.
- He can't go first.
- I'll go first.
- Okay.
- Do you want to go first?
Will you be okay?
- You should go first.
- Jae Seok should go first.
- You should...
- No.
Call it out at the sound of the timpani.
- Okay.
- Right.
Could you please...
play it one more time?
Again?
- I'm sorry.
(Walking over)
- Hold on. Let's practice.
- I'm sorry.
Let's practice first.
We can't end up like the previous session.
- That can't happen.
- Let's go!
- Will you play it again for us?
- With the cymbals.
- Right. With the cymbals.
Gosh, please.
(He plays the cymbals this time.)
- Here we go!
- Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 7.)
(7th try)
(Screaming)
- There we go. Hurry!
- There we go.
Five, four, three...
Oh, gosh.
I'm sorry.
(The aimless bullet becomes speechless.)
Right. We can't get excited.
We're ending up like the previous session.
- It's happening again.
- Let's use the chance this time.
- Right.
- I think the chance should be used.
- Right. Let's use the chance.
- Right.
(Chance)
There's one that isn't a chance.
I fail to win...
even when there are 3 winners out of 5.
(Curious)
- Lucky!
- "For this try,"
"white balls will get added."
- Two?
- Two!
- Nice!
One person can use three.
Two people can use two.
Then...
You should get one more.
- Right.
- Jae Won should get one more.
- No.
- I don't think...
- Well...
- No.
Let's pass the balls after seeing how we do.
Right. Let's do that.
- I see.
- Right.
You must not want to give it to Jae Won.
- That's not it.
- Right.
We'll pass it after seeing how we do.
- Let's go!
- We have to end it here.
We have to end it here.
(We have to end it here.)
(It's already the eighth try.)
(After getting two more balls, )
(will they be able to turn things around?)
- Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
Go!
(He got 3 balls at once.)
(He earns another ball.)
- Go.
- I think they will make it.
(8th try, Chance: 2 additional balls)
- We just need to get one each.
- Right.
Right.
Gosh!
Those are the ones left.
What?
(There are 2 balls left!)
- Five, four, - Gosh!
- three, two...
- We have one left.
We still have a chance!
(They fail with their eighth try.)
- I should've thrown harder.
- Gosh.
(They use up the chance so easily.)
I should've thrown harder.
Too bad.
- I should've thrown harder.
- That was our chance.
(That was disappointing.)
- I should've thrown harder.
- That was our chance.
That was our biggest chance.
It's okay.
There's this saying in music.
"Practice as if you're performing. Perform as if you're practicing."
- I'm sorry.
- Gosh.
Right. Don't feel nervous.
He wants us to do well like during practice.
One person should get at least one ball.
I can do it during practice.
- That's what it's like.
- It works during practice.
You start feeling nervous once the game begins.
- That's what it's like.
- It works during practice.
(It's this easy during practice.)
Let's do this. Let's give it a try.
- You should go first.
- Right.
I'll go second.
- Should I go third? Fourth?
- You should go fourth.
- Right.
- I'll go third.
Let's do a cheer.
- We have to make it this time.
- Let's do this.
One, two, three.
- Let's go!
Here we go!
- Ready.
- I'll go third.
Just a moment. I didn't say it yet.
- This is the ninth try.
- Do it with confidence.
- Here we go.
- Ready.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 9.)
- Here we go.
- Ready.
(9th try)
- That was nice.
- Gosh!
- Okay.
(Three balls were knocked down in one go again.)
Okay! Just one each!
There we go!
(Please!)
(9th try)
(Screaming)
(Rushing over)
(Jae Seok's neat finish)
What a relief!
(This is the table tennis master's final blow.)
(Hooray!)
- Round 2, success!
- Gosh, we did it!
- Gosh!
- We did it!
- All right. We did it!
- All right.
- So...
Round Two was a success.
You can stop now.
- Well, there's 1 try left.
- There's 1 try left.
Well, it's quite obvious.
- All right.
- You will lose everything.
- Stopping here is the best choice.
- Right.
Should I open it?
(Should I open the present for Round 3?)
But...
- You're not going to stop?
- Wait.
- There's one try left!
- You'll lose everything.
- But...
- You should stop here!
- You know that, don't you?
- Stop here!
There's one try left.
- Feel free to decide.
- We might make it.
Decide if you will stop or go.
Just a moment, please.
- Where is he going?
- Gosh.
I got so surprised after seeing him try to go.
Is someone there?
It's the instrument master.
- Right.
- I see. You talked with...
- the instrument master.
- Please make your decision.
(He talked with the master about whether to go or stop.)
One, two, three.
Stop.
I got so surprised.
- I got so surprised.
- Gosh.
- As a result, - Great work, everyone.
You will be given the presents for Round 1 and Round 2!
Thank you!
That was great.
- Thank you!
(The merchandise gets delivered with a delighted heart.)
- You can never know.
- Thank you.
(The great performance helped them as well.)
We were able to...
- We did it.
- make it in the end.
- I feel very proud.
- Right.
Gosh, that was like a drama.
We had the two stars of "Tazza."
It was an exciting day today.
- I had a blast.
- I had so much fun.
I've only watched the show on TV.
It was a great experience...
to meet many different people.
- I feel energized.
- Right.
I'll continue to work hard before I see you again.
Great. The Son of Incheon.
And you, Jae Won?
It was a great experience.
I've spent a happy day today.
I'll continue to work hard before I see you again. Bye!
(He copies his line.)
The reason I stopped...
was to thank the members...
who helped out with the shoot.
We will enjoy the drinks together.
(He shared the joy with his fellow members.)
Whenever Possible!
(Why won't a single one come when it says it's coming soon?)
(The town with a never-ending wait)
(This is South Chungcheong Province!)
(Is that why?)
(Whenever Possible in Chungcheong Province)
(Daughter of Chungcheong, Lee Sun Bin)
(The daughter of Cheonan...)
(is calm and composed.)
(The one who looks like an uncle during the holidays)
(Yoo Jae Myung, the one younger than Jae Seok)
What?
(The one younger by a year is polite.)
(It's hard for Jae Seok to call him comfortably.)
(The unexpected charms of the younger one)
(Run!)
(The carefree ones from Chungcheong are forced to run...)
(and put in shock.)
(That man's challenge)
(There's no time to be carefree...)
(during Cheonan's spare time.)
(Whenever Possible Season 5)